<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PSY490 Fall2023</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PSY490 Fall2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 1: Introduction / Orientation</title>
      <link>/2023/09/08/week-1-introduction-/-orientation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/09/08/week-1-introduction-/-orientation/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to PSY 490: Advanced current topics in neuroscience </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar Presentation Articles</title>
      <link>/2023/09/07/seminar-presentation-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/09/07/seminar-presentation-articles/</guid>
      <description>Pairs of students will lead a summary a summary / seminar-style discussion about the assigned weekly article.
Week 2 (September 15th): Quantification of Behaviour Article Link: Automated behavioural analysis reveals the basic behavioural repertoire of the urochordate Ciona intestinalis pdf Download Week 3 (September 22nd): Pharmacology Article Link: Activation of the dorsal, but not the ventral, hippocampus relieves neuropathic pain in rodents pdf Download Week 4 (September 29th): Molecular Endpoints Article Link: pdf download Week 5 (October 6th): SEQ Article Link: Neuronal activity-related transcription is blunted in immature compared to mature dentate granule cells pdf download Week 6 (October 20th): Electrophysiology Article Link: Group II metabotropic glutamate receptor expressing neurons in anterior cingulate cortex become sensitized after inflammatory and neuropathic pain pdf download Week 7 (October 27th): in-class test - no reading Week 8 (November 3rd): Alterations in gene expression Article Link: pdf download Week 9 (November 10th): DREADDs Article Link: pdf download Week 10 (November 17th): Optogenetics Article Link: pdf download Week 11 (November 24th): in-vivo calcium imaging Article Link: pdf download Week 12 (December 1st): TRAP Article Link: pdf download </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a website intended to simplify navigating content related to PSY 490. R codes used to generate this website are freely available on Github.
Original content prepared by Jennet Baumbach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
